Finding Aid for Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records, 1925-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Campers files 1925-1967
  - Chronological 1925-1967
    - 1939
      - Hare, Lauren Clark (Larry)
      - Knoroles, Jimmie
      - Lauver, Andrew Donald (Andy)
      - McPherson, Paul S. (includes Duncan and Rene)
      - Middleton, Blake
      - Monteith, Jimmy
      - Moore, Tommy
      - Penberthy, John (1939-1942)
      - Purcell, Bradford Moore
      - Tucker, David A.
    - 1940
      [Restricted until January 1 2040 ]
      - Baker, Russell (Box 9)
      - Barr, John
      - Brumbach, William P., Jr.
      - Case, Fred S.
      - Dye, John Van Ausdal
      - Hall, Bill
      - Hall, Joe
      - Hodges, James
      - Jordan, James
      - Jordan, Jerry H. (includes John)
      - Kretzschmar, Bill
      - Nehil, Thomas E.
      - Oakman, Charles Robert
      - Ruckelshaus, Jack
      - Slocum, Larry
      - Swainsons, Jillson [empty]
      - Thomas, John
      - Thompson, Tommy
      - Valade, Bob
      - Whiting, Peter
    - 1941
      [Restricted until January 1 2041 ]
      - Bartrop, James Jerome (Jerry) (1941-1942) (Box 9)
      - Bates, William O., III (Bill)
      - Bowen, Peter Francis
      - Brady, Peter
      - Duryea, Dick
      - Miller, Edward Kingsford (Ted)
      - Muirhead, Stanley N., Jr.
      - Packard, Charles E.
      - Reeves, Robert (includes John & Michael)
      - Robinson, Joseph L. (Joey)
      - Stroh, Eric Wetherill
      - Tucker, Randolph (Ranny)
      - Whitsell, Douglas S. (1941-1943)
      - Williams, Lawrence B. (1941-1942)
      - Willis, David Pearce (Dave)
      - Windisch, R. Humphrey
    - 1942
      [Restricted until January 1 2042 ]
      - Barton, Joseph Leonard (Box 10)
      - Brown, A. J. Terry, Jr.
      - Brown, William W.
      - Cook, Addison Porter
      - Duncan, Raymond
      - Funk, William Irvin G. (Bill)
      - Ganiard, Roderick F.
      - Genebach, Carleton (Skip) G.
      - Gutchess, Allen D., Jr.
      - Hendrie, Joseph M. (Joe)
      - Kretchmar, James Lauren
      - Leonard, Norman Harold
      - Lund, Bruce Reid
      - Malcolm, Karl Day
      - Morris, Frank Rockwell, Jr.
      - Nebel, Richard
      - Parsons, Donald Robert
      - Remien, Herbert Campbell
      - Sheets, Joseph Louis
      - Schwartz, Frank George
      - Spencer, Peter
      - Wagner, Robert Joel
    - 1943
      [Restricted until January 1 2043 ]
      - Andrews, Douglas W. (Box 10)
      - Andrews, Harold P.
      - Beamer, Jim Franklin
      - Betz, Roscoe, Jr.
      - Calhoon, Jack F.
      - Carrick, Bud
      - Desenberg, Charles M.
      - Desenberg, Milford M.
      - DeVilbis, Thomas Alexander
      - Field, Burke Rayner (includes Clarke Hills)
      - Ford, Mark
      - Hamilton, Schuyler
      - Hoffman, Peter Jay
      - Molloy, Peter H.
      - Montgomery, William Edward
      - O'Rourke, James
      - Pheatt, James Henry, III
      - Schulz, Paul Henry
      - Stranahan, Stephen
      - Walz, William Ludwig, Jr.
      - Yarnell, Joseph
    - 1944
      [Restricted until January 1 2044 ]
      - Barclay, Charles J. (Jerry) (Box 10)
      - Belote, James M.
      - Bennett, Kingsley
      - Beresford, John Booth
      - Biddle, John J.
      - Blanchard, Robert Edgar
      - Bleekman, Buzzie
      - Bowes, David Bigelow
      - Branion, Michael H. C.
      - Britner, Richard B.
      - Brown, Peter Truman
      - Bryant, John Arthur
      - Butterfield, Anthony Swindt
      - Craft, Robert David
      - Custer, Henry Jr.
      - Deacon, Richard W.
      - Dennison, David Severin
      - Dethmers, J. Robert
      - Drake, Robert Lincoln
      - Ettinger, Adrian Jr.
      - Farley, William David (Bill)
      - Fink, Peter Rupert
      - Foley, Norman K., Jr.
      - Ford, Robert Frazer
      - Frost, Albert C.
      - Frye, Carl Marvin
      - Garmey, Stephen
      - Hammond, James Warren
      - Hammond, Thomas Whipple
      - Hancock, David Alan
      - Handley, Edward William
      - Harris, John Bradley (includes David)
      - Hawley, Thomas Gardner III
      - Henning, A. Farnam
      - Herbert, William James
      - Hickham, Robert Thomas
      - Higbie, David Wing
      - Hill, David Gower
      - Hodges, John Barnett
      - Johnson, Richard Charles
      - Kaump, Donald Hunter (includes Robert & Jack)
      - Kurcz, Jerome (includes Robert)
      - Lanning, Walter Lon
      - Mac Rae, Robert Eugene
      - McCaffree, Charles (includes David)
      - McIntyre, Robert James
      - Morse, Peter
      - Ogilvie, James Donald
      - Parker, Alden Russell
      - Philbin, Patrick William
      - Rentschler, J. F. (Jeff) (1944-1949)
      - Rice, James Stanford
      - Riecker, John Ernest (includes James Charles)
      - Risk, Paul H., Jr.
      - Schruben, Ronald Lee
      - Shehan, James Phillip
      - Shelden, Henry D.
      - Sherer, Sam
      - Sikarovsky, Edmond Lee
      - Sloan, Malachi W., III
      - Stason, William Boaz
      - Stevens, William Frederic
      - Struever, Stuart McKee
      - Tallman, Edward R.
      - Taylor, James Morrison, Jr.
      - Tripp, William S. (Billy)
      - Van Alstyne, Johnnie
      - Volpe, Stanley L.
      - Walker, Harry Edward
      - Willey, Edward Norburn
      - Wilson, Donald Ralph
    - 1945
      [Restricted until January 1 2045 ]
      - Addison, James III (Box 11)
      - Albrecht, Frederick Robert
      - Barrett, Bill
      - Batsch, Frank W.
      - Beck, Frederick Walter
      - Beebe, Robert Alan
      - Benz, Robert Raymond
      - Bicknell, John Mark
      - Blach, Harold B., Jr.
      - Black, George Gilcrest
      - Bliss, Robert A.
      - Borgerson, Keith
      - Bradfield, John Jr.
      - Bushong, Ben
      - Butler, Edward Enwright, Jr.
      - Butt, Harold Luther
      - Caulkins, Henry Lewis II
      - Chase, William Byer II
      - Chevrie, Michael Manning (includes Owen James)
      - Collins, Donald Grant
      - Cooper, Robert J., Jr.
      - Darling, Gary Cyrenus Garrett III (includes David Payne)
      - Douglas, Robert Hugh
      - Foster, Hugh Mason, Jr.
      - Frye, Richard Emerson
      - Furman, Sherwood Murray (Woody)
      - Fuss, Robert Carson
      - Gelb, Thomas Alfred
      - Ginn, John Curtiss
      - Goetz, Angus Gerald, Jr. (Jerry)
      - Haman, Arthur Charles
      - Hoexter, Robert Henry
      - Holt, W. Stanley, Jr.
      - Hubbard, James Alfred (1945-1946)
      - Johnson, Richard D.
      - Jones, Samuel M. III
      - Kelter, Don L.
      - Kessel, William W.
      - Kidder, Laurence E.
      - Kressmann, Jacques
      - Lammert, Warren B., Jr.
      - Lathrop, Robert Curtiss
      - Lodish, Michael
      - Long, Theodore Dixon
      - Lorre, Dean Hendrickson
      - Ludington, Martin Lammert
      - Macauley, Edward Alvan
      - Martin, Richard H.
      - McConnell, Thomas Royce
      - Meland, Richard Denny
      - Mitchell, Irving Stuart
      - Moss, David Francis
      - Niehuss, John Marvin
      - Painter, Don Charles
      - Perry, Clair
      - Reindel, George John III
      - Rickert, Herbert Elvin
      - Roscoe, Richard Powell
      - Sherman, George Wilson (Joe)
      - Sisson, Edward Brunck
      - Skillman, Harry (Butch)
      - Stowe, Frederick Taylor II
      - Tann, Donald Wittman
      - Taylor, John Ripley
      - Villerot, George E.
      - Volpe, Salvatore
      - Wensinger, Charles Franklin
      - Williamson, Richard Lee
      - Willson, Jay Curtis
      - Wiseman, Thomas Wetzler, Jr.
    - 1946
      [Restricted until January 1 2046 ]
      - Adcock, Howard (Box 11)
      - Atkins, Thomas M.
      - Bailey, Edmond I.
      - Barnard, Hugh Neil
      - Beardsley, Robert Buchanan
      - Buhl, Larry
      - Cameron, Robert Bruce
      - Cook, George S.
      - Couper, Thomas Edward
      - Cushing, James B.
      - Fauster, John (Jack)
      - Ficks, Lee B.
      - Flourney, Lev. Jr.
      - Freeland, John
      - Glover, George H., Jr.
      - Goetz, Albert G., Jr.
      - Gounsley, Dennis E.
      - Healey, Tony (1946-1947)
      - Kleis, John C.
      - Lashmet, Michael H. (1946-1947)
      - Machus, Robert
      - Maxwell, J. Robert
      - McManus, Jimmy
      - Reinert, Owen (Staff 1946)
    - 1947
      [Restricted until January 1 2047 ]
      - Anderson, Marc B. (Box 11)
      - Anderson, Frederich Reid
      - Avery, Frederick D., Jr.
      - Blake, Eugene (includes Peter)
      - Breuer, Walter
      - Buskirk, George
      - Domke, John Philip
      - Enck, Charles Francis
      - Fisher, Walter Briggs
      - Frendreis, Richard Joseph
      - Giannaris, James S.
      - Hickox, Charles Chatterton "Chat"
      - Kales, Robert Gray, Jr.
      - Kerr, Henry Hampton, III
      - Kersey, Robert Evans
      - Knaggs, Howard
      - Loebel, Andre Henri
      - Lynch, Jerry David (1947-1949)
      - Merseles, Craig Philip (Box 12)
      - Meyers, Gerson Ellis
      - Orwig, John Scott, Jr. (Scotty) (1947-1952)
      - Reynolds, C. Kelly, III
      - Server, David Lee (Bud) (1947-1949)
      - Stumb, Charles E. (includes William Thomas)
      - Thompson, Guy Bradley
      - Whyel, George L., Jr.
      - Will, Thomas Sherman (Tom) (1947-1949)
    - 1948
      [Restricted until January 1 2048 ]
      - Batdorff, Jack (Box 12)
      - Belknap, Charles Lewis (Chuck (1948-1949)
      - Benson, Rupert Hazelton
      - Bishop, Leonard James (Jimmie)
      - Burr, Henry (includes Walter)
      - Chidsey, Herbert Malott
      - Denham, Roger
      - Folger, Thomas K.
      - Gallogly, William George
      - Glancy, Alfred Robinson (Robin) (1948-1949)
      - Graham, Robert J. (Bobby) (1948-1949)
      - Hammond, Rudolph E. (includes Peter S.)
      - Healey, Graham
      - Jones, Parry
      - Kaine, Lawrence Francis
      - Keyes, Ralph Clark, Jr.
      - LeRoy, Robert Bradford (Bob) (1948-1949)
      - Lippincott, Dallas (includes Charles)
      - Pence, John Leavitt (Pete) (1948-1949)
      - Thrasher, Steven Duane (Steve) (1948-1949)
    - 1949
      [Restricted until January 1 2049 ]
      - Betz, Frederic (Fritz) (1948-1949) (Box 12)
      - Bokhof, Henry Steel, Jr. (includes Dick & Ted) (1949-1950)
      - Burton, Paul Leonard, Jr.
      - Byrne, Dan (Danno)
      - Cashman, John Henry (Jack) (1946-1949)
      - Clark, Lindley Edward, Jr. (Eddie)
      - Cook, Richard M. (Cookie)
      - Cooper, Forster (includes John Robert)
      - Creden, John T. (Jack)
      - Crosier, Ray
      - Cummings, Thomas Frederick (Tom)
      - de Koning, Kendrik John (Kim) (1948-1949)
      - DeVilbiss, James Bond (Jim)
      - Dinan, John T., Jr.
      - Dudley, William Taber (Bill)
      - Dunin, Stanley Edward (Stas)
      - Falconer, Robert Daniels (Bobby)
      - Fentress, James Francis, Jr. (Jim)
      - Fletcher, Ralph G. (1948-1949)
      - Foley, John Russell
      - Gausewitz, Karl
      - Geller, Peter Tolman (Pete) (includes Michael Daniel) (1949-1950)
      - Griffin, William Joseph, Jr. (Bill) (includes Hollis & Roger) (1949-1953)
      - Haass, Frederick (Fritz)
      - Hyde, Andrew Cornwall (Andy) (includes Fritz)
      - Johnston, Donald Byrne (Don) (includes Bill) (1949-1955)
      - Johnston, James Clarke, Jr. (Jimmy)
      - Kearney, Stephen W. (Steve)
      - Keen, Charles Willard, III (Bubby)
      - Kendrick, Ben Joseph (Ben)
      - Klores, Stanley Whitehouse (Stan)
      - McMillin, Robert Edward (Bob)
      - Marks, David Owen (Dave)
      - Martin, Gary Schatz (Butch)
      - Martin, Patrick M. (Pat) (1949-1950)
      - Morgan, Philip Smith (Phil) (1946-1949)
      - Morton, James Townsend (Jimmy)
      - Pollock, Frank Gordon (Frank)
      - Potter, Doran Peter
      - Richardson, David Riley
      - Ridley, (Robert) Roy (1948-1949)
      - Rovner, David Mark
      - Russell, William S. (Bill)
      - Schultz, Paul Herbert
      - Smith, Michael J. (Mike) (1948-1949)
      - Smith, Rayburn Ross (Ross)
      - Taylor, Thomas W.
      - Tope, Harry Earle (Earle) (Box 13)
      - Wade, Morrison Theodore (Ted)
      - Weis, Thomas Thedieck (Tom)
      - Wheeler, William Truesdale (Trues)
      - Wiese, Joseph Frederic, Jr. (Freddy)
      - Williamson, George H.
      - Wolf, David Robert (Dave) (1945-1949)
      - Zybell, Bert William (Billy) (1948-1949)
    - 1950
      [Restricted until January 1 2050 ]
      - Affleck, William C. (Bill) (1949) (Box 13)
      - Allen, Jim
      - Appel, Kenny
      - Archangeli, Johnny
      - Baumgardner, Grant
      - Bixby, Charles D. (Danny) (1947 1948 1950)
      - Boehmer, Gustave
      - Brown, Donald Guerry (Don)
      - Caple, Al
      - Casaroll, Tony
      - Christy, Danny
      - Curby, Johnny
      - Dayton, Daniel Denison, Jr. (Danny) (1949)
      - Deibel, Dixie
      - DeGowin, Dick (1946 1950)
      - Drew, Tom [EMPTY]
      - Dungan, Al (includes Tom) (1950 1953)
      - Edgar, Pete (includes Mike)
      - Finton, Robert James (Bob) (1949)
      - Gove, Robert (Robbie)
      - Greenley, Don
      - Greenspan, Howard
      - Haynes, Harley
      - Hiebert, John (1945 1946, 1947 1950)
      - Horn, Steve
      - Hudson, Jeffery MacLaren (Jeff) (1949)
      - Jackson, John
      - Killian, Butch
      - King, Don
      - Kretchmar, Richard Herman (Dick)
      - LaCoe, Steve
      - Lavan, Martin Brian (Pat) (includes Sean Desmond) (1949)
      - Luckett, Pace
      - MacKinnon, Charles
      - MacLeod, William (Billy) (1949)
      - Mahoney, Jeremiah William (Jerry) (1949)
      - Marshall, John Waller (Johnny)
      - McEvoy, James (Jimmy)
      - Merritt, Buck
      - Miller, Duncan R. (Petie) (1949)
      - Montgomery, Mead
      - Nelson, Bob
      - Newstedt, George Edward (1949)
      - Outhwaite, Joe
      - Pemberton, Tom
      - Prentis, John
      - Ramsay, Dave
      - Schuler, Hans (includes Jim) (1953)
      - Score, Alvin
      - Sellers, Gary
      - Simmons, Ted
      - Singer, Dan
      - Sinz, Peter
      - Sullivan, Art
      - Webster, Pete
      - Wheelock, John C.
    - 1951
      [Restricted until January 1 2051 ]
      - Allen, John (includes Steve) (Box 14)
      - Backus, Mike
      - Berner, Bob
      - Brown, Robbie (includes Rickie)
      - Brust, Jack
      - Camara-Peon, Pat
      - Chambers, Rick
      - Colombo, Rickey
      - De Garmo, Pete
      - Denise, Doug (includes Dick and Jerry) (1951-1952)
      - Elliot, Charlie (includes Tom)
      - Eversman, Walt
      - Gallagher, Tim
      - Geitgey, Joe
      - Gilpin, Jim
      - Gittleman, Jimmy
      - Goes, Jose (includes Eduardo)
      - Gotz, Thomas Allan
      - Grant, Lex
      - Grass, Roger
      - Grinnell, Tom
      - Gugenheim, Bob
      - Haynes, Woody
      - Heinemann, Fred
      - Hodgson, Rich
      - Hogan, Jeff (includes Clem)
      - Holmes, Dave
      - Hughes, Ted (includes Robbie)
      - Hunter, Sandy
      - Kingsley, Tom
      - Koch-Weser, Peter
      - Kreimer, Tony
      - Larson, Walt (includes Clyde)
      - Lichty, Bill
      - Litow, Rickey
      - Marsh, Dave
      - Myers, Fritz
      - Niehuss, John
      - Norton, Chuck
      - Patterson, Dave (includes Don)
      - Pugh, Bill
      - Schnute, Bill (includes Carl and Jamie) (1951-1955)
      - Schweitzer, Bobby
      - Shine, Dan
      - Slayton, Butch
      - Sleight, John
      - Slezak, Dave
      - Smith, Hank
      - Smith, Butch
      - Spencer, Jack
      - Sprague, Jim
      - Stevens, Bill
      - Stewart, Sandy (includes Pete) (1950-1951)
      - Stewart, Tom
      - Thompson, Bill
      - Thompson, Johnny
      - Weiner, Vic
      - Welke, Bob
      - West, Johnny
      - White, Tom
      - Woolner, Bunny
      - Wright, Jay
      - Wright, Jim
    - 1952
      [Restricted until January 1 2052 ]
      - Amalfitano, Neil (Box 14)
      - Buchart, Jim
      - Cahow, John
      - Collins, Peter (includes George)
      - Davies, Jim
      - Drackett, Danny
      - Folger, Bill
      - Goodrich, Jimmy (includes Bobby)
      - Hall, Geoffrey (Box 15)
      - Henry, Brian
      - Holmes, Gordon Oesterling
      - Hubly, Bill
      - Jennings, Harry
      - Kaatz, Dick
      - Kleinschmit, Arthur
      - Kollen, Mike (includes Pete) (1952-1953)
      - Kroeber, Dick
      - DeHaan, Jon
      - Lentini, Dick
      - May, Stuart
      - Nagel, Eddie
      - Nebel, Charles
      - Newman, Mel
      - Norman, Allen E.
      - Perkins, Jim
      - Pettit, Bill
      - Petty, Lenny
      - Price, Hickman (High) (includes Marston)
      - Obert, Don
      - Richards, Edward
      - Riebenack, Pete
      - Riecker, Teddy
      - Roberts, Doug
      - Salisbury, Dick
      - Scherer, Walt
      - Sharrock, Jack (includes Dave)
      - Slocombe, Walter
      - Stahl, John T.
      - Stepan, Paul (includes John)
      - Thomas, Jim
      - Tompkins, Bob
      - Vogt, Clifford (Sandy) (includes Pete)
      - Wade, Allen (includes Mark)
      - Wetherby, Steve
      - Whiting, Jock
      - Wood, Neil (includes Winston "Winnie") (1948-1954)
      - Wright, Jimmy (includes Teddy)
    - 1953
      [Restricted until January 1 2053 ]
      - Anderson, Buzz (Box 15)
      - Arnold, Bob (includes John) (1953-1954)
      - Bartlowe, Sterling
      - Bedford, Mike
      - Bigelow, Timothy Lawson (Tim) 1949
      - Bouchey, Jimmie
      - Brandt, Ricky
      - Cook, Dave
      - Curtis, Boots
      - Davis, Steve (includes Harve)
      - Fischer, Rich (includes Dave) (1953-1955)
      - Fowler, Jack (includes James Harold "Jimmy") (1953-1957)
      - Gentry, Howard (includes Tommy) (1953-1954)
      - Grady, Michael (includes Steve) (1953-1955)
      - Greiner, Tony
      - Herrick, Todd
      - Hoobler, Raymond
      - Howell, Bob
      - Johnson, Tom
      - Kelly, Donny
      - King, George
      - Leach, Bob
      - Lewis, Dave
      - Mahar, Jim
      - Mayne, Joe
      - McGuire, Johnny (includes Michael)
      - McMillin, Jamie
      - Montague, Bob
      - Murphy, Mark
      - Norman, Anthony
      - O'Connor, Johnny
      - O'Shaughnessy, Tim
      - Parke, Charlie & Clement (Box 16)
      - Pfeiffer, Craig
      - Poirier, Alex
      - Post, Mike (includes Jerry) (1953-1955)
      - Rezanka, John Charles
      - Risdon, Dick (includes Tom) (1951-1953)
      - Rudell, Bill
      - Sacks, Frankie
      - Sager, Dudley (includes Dave & Doug) (1951-1953)
      - Schmidt, Gary
      - Schreur, Dave (includes Ammon Jeffrey "Jeff") (1953-1957)
      - Seyffert, Eddie (1951)
      - Smith, James Allen
      - Smith, Preston Walker (1949)
      - Stanford, Skip
      - Stewart, Davey (includes Bobby)
      - Quinn, Lawrence R.
      - Tiernan, Tom
      - VanderVeen, Jimmy
      - Weymouth, Butch
    - 1954
      [Restricted until January 1 2054 ]
      - Adams, Morrie (Box 16)
      - Alfenito, John
      - Andreae, Frank
      - Avery, Toby
      - Branion, Bobby
      - Cain, Steve
      - Carpenter, Johnny
      - Cooper, Jim
      - Cramton, Gary
      - Crutchfield, Woody
      - Curtis, Mack
      - Detwiler, Johnny
      - Elliott, Davie
      - Emmett, John P.
      - Furstenberg, Bill
      - Garza, Bobby
      - Griffin, Joe
      - Grimm, Bob (includes Dick) (1954-1955)
      - Harrison, Mac
      - Imbrie, Will
      - Keller, Joe
      - Lenz, Ricky
      - Levine, Tommy
      - Levy, Joe
      - Link, Roy
      - McKay, Rusty
      - O'Neill, Bob
      - Polster, David
      - Rahilly, Larry
      - Ratterman, Tommy (includes Bambi, Mike)
      - Roe, Johnny
      - Self, Bill (1955)
      - Simmons, Dave
      - Smiggen, Bob
      - Stearns, Clark
      - Stebbins, Dickie
      - Stoll, Brian
      - Stolorow, Mark
      - Todd, Chuck (includes Jim)
      - VanHouten, Buzzy (includes Pete)
      - Walker, Bob
      - Walker, Wink
      - Wardwell, Johnny
      - White, Alec
      - Whitehead, Jeff
      - Wilson, Jim
      - Wilson, Stan (includes Bob)
      - Winchester, Frank
    - 1955
      [Restricted until January 1 2055 ]
      - Adcock, Johnny (Box 16)
      - Addison, Robbie
      - Allen, Jim
      - Badger, Graeme
      - Baldwin, Teddy
      - Bergstrom, Van
      - Bertling, Bill
      - Bogen, David
      - Borusch, Bob
      - Bosch, Chuckie
      - Bradley, Tommy (includes Bruce) (1955-1956)
      - Bremer, Joey
      - Broeman, Rol (includes Billy)
      - Burcaw, Kenny (includes Bobby)
      - Cassell, Jim (includes Bill)
      - Cheley, Don
      - Clark, Bill
      - Clayton, Tommy (Box 17)
      - Clements, Mike
      - Colker, Dick
      - Cook, Stan
      - Daniels, Dick
      - Dillman, Dave
      - Dittman, Robbie
      - Downes, Mike
      - Earl, Dick
      - Eberts, Jerry (includes Billy)
      - Ellstrom, Ole
      - Estes, Curt
      - Foster, Jim
      - Gregory, Doug (includes Rich)
      - Griswold, Joe
      - Gurdjian, Ron (includes Ricky) (1954-1955)
      - Gusfa, Connie
      - Heames, Bob
      - Helfrick, Charles
      - Hummer, Joe
      - Irons, Bruce
      - Irwin, John (includes Win)
      - Keegan, Bob
      - Kelson, John (includes Dave)
      - Kraus, Gene
      - LaPointe, Frank J.
      - Leach, Bob
      - Leighton, John
      - Lindell, Doug (includes Charley)
      - MacHarg, Davy
      - MacIntyre, Dennis
      - MacKay, Jack
      - McClure, Clyde
      - McCune, Chuck
      - Miles, Mike
      - Miller, Jeff
      - Moloney, Paul
      - Nelles, Wally
      - Parke, Chuck (includes Clem)
      - Plowman, Tommy
      - Price, Jim
      - Rassas, George (includes Kevin & Nicholas "Doc")
      - Reed, Mike (includes Dave)
      - Rice, Johnny (includes Tom)
      - Richardson, Don
      - Risdon, Russ
      - Rosenfeld, Davey (includes Mark)
      - Sangster, Bobby
      - Schmidt, Bill
      - Shafer, Butch
      - Slessman, D. B.
      - Stanford, Lou
      - Steed, Bucky
      - Steffans, Eddie
      - Stites, Johnny
      - Tan, Eng
      - Tennant, Derk
      - Wear, Duke
      - Welch, Jimmy (includes Craig Jr.) (1954-1955)
      - Wiggins, William James, III (Bill)
      - Wilcox, Frankie
      - Williams, Rick
      - Woodworth, Fred L. (1957)
      - Wright, Sherm
    - 1956
      [Restricted until January 1 2056 ]
      - Andrews, Pete (Box 18)
      - Bailey, David
      - Baker, Lee
      - Beard, Louis
      - Butcher, Kenny
      - Carter, Johnny
      - Cassidy, Kevin
      - Clark, Joe
      - Crouse, Timmy (includes Peter) (1956-1962)
      - Curtiss, Carl (Curt)
      - Dalton, Norman Perry
      - Dascola, David (includes Robert Michael "Bobby") (1956-1958)
      - Fletcher, Steve
      - Forkner, Jim
      - Fortino, Steve
      - Gordon, Brit (includes Tracy & Scotty)
      - Greene, Geoff
      - Heritier, Dave
      - Hinderer, Jim
      - Holland, Jeep (includes Jomp) (1956-1957)
      - Jones, Jay
      - Lapham, Bruce
      - Lasch, Larry
      - Lee, Billy
      - Lincoln, Rusty
      - Lyon, Chuck
      - Mahaffey, Mark
      - Mahon, John
      - McKay, Tad (includes George Wm. Jr.) (1956-1957)
      - Moore, Lee (includes Frank & George) (1956-1958)
      - Ogley, Bill
      - Oliver, John
      - Penrose, Clem
      - Pletscher, Hank
      - Searles, Barry
      - Seyffert, Gordon
      - Sisson, Lance
      - Skae, Ned
      - Sullivan, Mark
      - Tally, Truman
      - Thompson, Dave
      - Thompson, Pete
      - Watkins, Hamilton
      - Welch, Gale
      - Willie, Roice (includes Brent Stanley & Stan Curtis) (1956-1963)
    - 1957
      [Restricted until January 1 2057 ]
      - Benner, Al (Box 18)
      - Blackburn, Jeffery H. (Jeff)
      - Blackstone, George
      - Boyer, Tom (includes Frank "Hank") (1957-1958)
      - Breer, Bert (includes Carl)
      - Brown, Clinton
      - Bruggeman, Tonton "Tony" (includes Pappy, Henry, Jack Anthony, Joseph, Patrick J.) (1957-1961)
      - Burks, Ned
      - Campbell, Darrell (Skip)
      - Campbell, Don Alan
      - Cauchois, Gage
      - Coe, Sandy
      - Cord, Cameron Wayne (Corky)
      - Cunningham, Charles Frederick "Fred"
      - Early, Steve
      - Evans, Robert Jr.